Anyone who's watching without judgment, I feel like they understand, like, she's panicking because something very real is happening and she is at her wits end.
Like, she's now, like, calling on the world.
He started crying and I said, Joey, and they started asking me, was he gonna die?
And I was just like, you know, then the kids were here and they were hearing him say that.
And I was just like, we gotta figure it out.
Because right around the corner, they're looting.
Hopefully, you know, if we call 911 again, they can come and help you.
And I'm like, cool.
And she's like, oh, they're on snowblowers.
And I'm looking at the, I can see, looking through my window, I can see the corner.
So I'm like, okay, you know, we might be on to something.
Maybe if we can get him to a, to where this looting is going on, maybe we can get him some help.
I mean, if they can put down TVs down the street, I know we can pull Joe.